nfcu.com 2014-12-31

# FACTS

                                                                                                                               Rev. 7/13
 FACTS                 WHAT DOES NAVY FEDERAL DO
                       WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
 Why?                  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the
                       right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and
                       protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
 What?                 The types of personal information that we collect and share depend on the product or service that you
                       have with us. This information can include:
                       • Social Security Number and income
                       • Account balances and payment history
                       • Account transactions and checking account information
                       When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
 How?                  All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday businesses. In
                       the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information,
                       whether Navy Federal chooses to share, and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                                           Does Navy Federal         Can you limit
 Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                                                           share?                    this sharing?
 For our everyday business purposes–
 such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to                            Yes                  No
 court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes–                                                                           Yes                  No
 to offer our products and services to you
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                                                    Yes                  No
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–                                                       Yes                  No
 information about your transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–                                                       No             We don’t share
 information about your creditworthiness
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                                    No             We don’t share
 Questions?            Call toll-free 1-888-842-6328 or go to navyfederal.org.
© 2013 Navy Federal NFCU 198 (7-13)
en

    Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?  Navy Federal Credit Union; Navy Federal Financial Group, LLC; Navy Federal Brokerage
                               Services, LLC; and Navy Federal Asset Management, LLC
What we do
How does Navy Federal          To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security
                               measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and
protect my personal
                               secured files and buildings.
information?
                               Navy Federal regularly tests and assesses its information security measures, systematically
                               trains employees, and adopts upgrades and enhancements as necessary to protect your
                               information.
How does Navy Federal          We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
                               • Open an account or deposit money
collect my personal
                               • Pay your bills or apply for a loan
information?                   • Use your credit or debit card
                               We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                               affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
                               • Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your
                                  creditworthiness
                               • Affiliates from using your information to market to you
                               • Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                               State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                     Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                               non-financial companies.
                               • Our affiliates include companies with a Navy Federal name; financial companies such
                                  as Navy Federal Credit Union; Navy Federal Financial Group, LLC; Navy Federal
                                  Brokerage Services, LLC; and Navy Federal Asset Management, LLC.
Nonaffiliates                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                               non-financial companies.
                               • Navy Federal does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                               financial products or services to you.
                               • Our joint marketing partners include investment, insurance, and other financial
                                  services companies.
